Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - Addendum
    Davis, Willie
    DeBlulger, L.D.
    DeComathiere, A.B.
    DeCoy, Robert
    DeLavalade, Herman
    Dennis, E.M.
    Depaur, Len
    Dern, Bruce
    DeWindt, Hal
    Dickerson, Dudley
    Dixon, Ivan
    Dones, Sidney Preston
    Downs, Johnny
    Dudley, S.H.
    Dumas, Wade
    Duncan, Todd
    Dunn, William H.B.
    Duval, Al
    Dyer, E.C.
    E
    Carly, John
    Eckstine, Ronnie
    Edmondson, William
    Edwards, James
    Edwards, Johnny
    English, E.
    Ennis, Floyd
    Errol, Leon
    Etula, ASa
    Evans, Russelle (Bob Evans)
    F
    Fantauzzi, John
    Farina (Haskins, A.)
    Farr, Mel
    Feltenburg, Henry
    Felton, Bostic
    Fenderson, Reginald
    Ferniel, Dan
    Fetchit, Steppin (L.T. Perry)
    Flennoy, Lorence
    Fletcher, Orville
    Flowers, Theodor (Tiger)
    Fluellen, Joel
    Foster, William
    Fountaine, William
    Fox, John
    Foxx, Redd
    Franklin, Bo
    Frazier, Dan
    Frederick, Leon
    Frederick, Hal
    Freeman, Al Jr.
    Freeman, Ernie
    Freeman, Kenneth
    Fullback
    Fuller, James
    Fuller, Walter
    G
    Gaines, Harris
    Gampu, Ken
    Gant, Harry
    Gantt, Hermann
    Gilden, Richard
    Gilliam, Stu
    Gilpin, Charles, S.
    Gleaver, Abraham
    Glenn, Roy
    Goden, Freemon (Amos)
    Godfrey, George
    Godfrey, Sam
    Gor, Fred
    Goss, Bobby
    Gossett, Lou
    Grant, Alfred
    Grant, Arthur
    Graves, Jessie A.
    Gray, Harry
    Green, Otis
    Green, Rueben
    Greenwood, Rene (Child)
    Gregory, Dick
    Gregory, Guy
    Grier, Roosevelt
    Griffith, Douglas
    Griner, Lawrence
    Guilford, Willbur L.
    Gunn, Bill
    Gunn, Moses
    H
    Hairston, Jester
    Hairston, William
    Hall, John
    Hamilton, George W.
    Kipp, Hamilton
    Hannibal, Marc
    Hardin, Ira
    Hardwick, Leon H.
    Harker, Gordan
    Harrington, Hamtree
    Harris, Bud
    Harris, Clifford
    Harris, Darrell
    Harris, Paul
    Hart, Fred
    Hastings, Henry E.
    Hutton, Temple
    Hawkins, Charles
    Hawley, Monte
    Hayes, Malcolm (Little Mac)
    Haynes, Daniel
    Haynes, Leroy
    Haynes, Lloyd
    Haze, Jonathan
    Heath, Gordon
    Heath, Mark
    Henderson, Harry
    Hepburn, Phillip
    Herman, Will (Kid)
    Hernandez, Juano
    Herndon, Cleo
    Hightower, Harold (Child)
    Hill, Craig
    Hill, Pickaninny
    Hill, Stephen
    Holder, Roland
    Hooks, Robert
    Hope, Boots
    Hoskins, Allen (Farina)
    House, Mack
    Howard, Shingzie
    Howard, Vince
    Hunter, R.
    Hurd, Hugh
    Hurtle, Kurt
    Hyman, Earle
    Hyson, Robert
    I
    Ingram, Clifford
    Ingram, Rex
    J
    Jackson, Al
    Jackson, Dan
    Jackson, Earl
    Jackson, Eugene, Jr.
    Jackson, Eugene, Sr.
    Jackson, Freddie
    Jackson, Horace
    James, Clifton
    James, Leon
    Jeanette, Joe
    Jeffries, Herb
    John, Errol
    John, Ben E. Dr.
    Johnson, Bob
    Johnson, Dots
    Johnson, Julius
    Johnson, John Lester
    Johnson, Kyle
    Johnson, Noble
    Johnson, Rafer
    Johnson, William
    Jones, Chester
    Jones, Darby
    Jones, Gus
    Jones, Ike
    Jones, James Earl
    Jones, Judd
    Jones, Matthew
    Jones, Robert Earle
    Jones, Roland
    Jones, Sigsbee (Child)
    Jones, Thaddus
    Julian, Hubert, F.
    Julien, Max
    Juma (Child)
    K
    Kalu, Kalu (Child)
    Killebrew, Frank
    Kilpatrick, Lincoln
    Kincaid, Jeremiah (Child)
    King, Elmer
    King, Webb
    Kingi, Henry
    Kings, Samba
    Kirby, John
    Kirksey, Kirk
    Kitzmiller, John
    Kotto, Yaphet
    Kunoch, Ngarla
    Kya-Hill, Robert
    L
    LaMar, Lawrence
    Lamphius, Roy
    Langford, Sam
    Lanier, Eric (Child)
    Ledbetter, Leo
    Lee, Canada
    Lee, Carl
    Lee, John D.
    Lee, Russell
    Lewis, Ferdie
    Lewis, Louis
    Lewis, Sandy
    Liston, Sonny
    Little, Cleavon
    Lloyd, William
    Lockhart, Calvin
    Long, Walter
    Loud, Rommie
    Lourant, Arthur Chico
    Lovejoy, Alec
    Lowe, Edmund
    Lowe, James B.
    Lucas, George
    Luncy, LaMar
    Lynn, Jay Loft
    M
    McCain, Billy
    McCalla, Vernon
    McCann, Thomas
    McClane, Paul
    McDaniels, Sam
    McGarrity, Everett
    McGlory, Margee
    Mack, Tom
    McKinney, Jake
    Macklin, Clifton
    Maggio, Angelo
    Mahon, Carl
    Marchall, Don
    Marques, Evaristo
    Marriott, John
    Marshall, Charles
    Marshall, Don
    Marshall, Lloyd
    Marshall, William
    Martin, D'Urville
    Martin, Orlando
    Martin, Roy
    Mason, John
    Mayes, Johnnie
    Mayes, Preston
    Mayfield, Julian
    Mayo, Whitney
    Mello, Breno
    Michael, Daniel
    Mickelby, Rexarian
    Miller, Doris (Dorie)
    Miller, Flournoy
    Mills, Michael
    Milton, William
    Mitchell, Aaron
    Mitchell, Don
    Mitchell, Scoey
    Moore, Archie
    Moore, Charles
    Moore, Edward
    Moore, Tim (Kingfish)
    Moore, Tommie
    Morehouse, Clarence
    Moreland, Mantan
    Morris, Earl J.
    Morris, Greg
    Morrison, Sammy
    Morse, Roy
    Moseley, Irving
    Moseley, Thomas
    Munroe, Neville
    Muse, Clarence
    N
    Nagel, George
    Narcisse, Joe
    N'Degwa, Afred
    Nelson, Felix
    Nero, Curtis
    Nicholas, Fayard
    Nooman, Tommy
    Norris, Edward
    Nubraet, Serge
    O
    Okunoyama, George
    Olden, Charles
    O'Neal, Frederick
    O'Neil, Walter
    Owens, Virgil
    P
    Page, Harrison
    Parrish, John
    Patrick, E.
    Patterson, Warren
    Paul, Ike
    Payne, Jimmy
    Payton, Lew
    Pearson, Johnny
    Perdue, Leon
    Perez, Raoul
    Perry, Steve (Child)
    Persoff, Nehemiah
    Peter, Brock
    Peterson, Caleb
    Petway, Bruce
    Phillips, Ferman
    Phillips, Hilton
    Phillips, Roy
    Pickett, Bill
    Pierson, Don
    Pleasant, Henry
    Poitier, Sidney
    Polk, Oscar
    Portman, Eric
    Powell, William J.
    Pringle, Conrod
    Proctor, John
    Prymus, Kenneth
    Pryor, H.L.
    Pryor, Jack
    Pryor, Richard
    R
    Ramsey, Ben
    Randall, George
    Ray, Arthur
    Ray, Jackie (hoo)
    Redd, Clarence
    Redfield, William
    Reed, George
    Renard, Ken
    Reynolds, Eli
    Rhodes, Hari
    Rice, Breland
    Rich, Ron
    Riley, Jay
    Rivers, Fletcher
    Roberts, Davis
    Robertson, J.A.
    Robeson, Paul
    Robinson, Bill
    Robinson, Chips
    Robinson, Dewey
    Robinson, Hayes
    Robinson, James
    Robinson, Sugar Ray
    Rochester
    Rodriquez, Percy
    Rosamond, Clinton
    Ross, Clinton
    Roundtree, Richard
    Roye, Philip
    Rudd, Wellman
    Russell, Sam
    Rust, Richard
    Ruthford, John
    S
    Sadler, Sam
    Sailes, Robert A. (Child)
    St. Jacques, Raymond
    St. Thomas, Tony
    Salles, Bobby (Child)
    Satten, Lonnie
    Scott, Leslie
    Scott, Ray
    Scott, Sylvester
    Scott, Tom
    Sekka, Johnny
    Shackleford, Lloyd
    Shannon, Alex K.
    Sheffield, Maceo
    Shields, Frank
    Silvera, Frank
    Simpson, Walter
    Skillet, Bug-Eyed
    Skinner, Herbert
    Slator, Mark
    Slaughter, Vernon
    Slim, Memphis
    Smart, Bobby (Child)
    Smith, Earl
    Smith, Eddie
    Smith, Elwood
    Smith, Ernest
    Smith, Henry
    Smith, James R.
    Smith, Jeli
    Smith, Jimmie
    Smith, Leon
    Smith, Leonard
    Smith, Norris
    Smith, Oscar
    Smith, Roy
    Smith, T.D.
    Smith, Tommie
    Snowball (McHenry, Curtis)
    Southern, Tom
    Spearman, Rawa
    Spell, George
    Spencer, Kenneth
    Sproul, Newt
    Sterman, Otto
    Stevens, Lonnie
    Stewart, Nicodemus
    Stewart, Samuel
    Stokes, Al
    Strode, Woody
    Sunshine Sammy (F.E. Morrison)
    T
    Takahashi (Child)
    Tate, John
    Tatum, E.G.
    Teal, Joel
    Thomas, James
    Thomas, John
    Thomas, Reed
    Thompson, Creighton
    Thompson, Edward
    Thompson, Harry
    Thompson, Slim
    Towler, Dan
    Tracy, Harry
    Trotter, Uncle Pleasant
    True, Ernest
    Tudawali, Robert
    Turman, Glynn
    Turner, John
    Turner, Martin
    Turner, Raymond
    Turner, Smoke
    Turpin, Ben
    Tutt, Homer J.
    U
    Usher, James
    V
    Venerable, Paul
    Vernon, Lou
    Verwayne, Percy
    W
    Walker, Bill
    Wallace, Coley
    Ward, Richard
    Warfield, William
    Washington, Blue
    Washington, John B.
    Washington, Kenneth
    Watson, Deek
    Webster, Peter
    Wessell, Henri
    West, Charles A.
    West, George
    Whipper, Leigh
    White, Ernest
    White, Jack
    White, Walter, Jr.
    Whitfield, Charles
    Whitfield, Robert (Smoke)
    Whiting, Napoleon
    Whitman, Ernest
    Williams, Bert
    Williams, Billy Dee
    Williams, Bob
    Williams, Clarence III
    Williams, Clyde
    Williams, Danny
    Williams, Duke
    Williams, John
    Williams, Milton
    Williams, Owen
    Williams, Richard
    Williams, Robert
    Williams, Spencer, Jr.
    Williams, Spencer, Sr.
    Williams, Virgil
    Williams, Zack
    Williamson, Fred
    Wilson, Arthur
    Wilson, Charles
    Wilson, Clarence
    Wilson, Dooley
    Wilson, Ernest
    Wilson, Frank
    Wilson, Lawrence
    Wilson, Scott
    Winfield, Paul
    Wolcott, George
    Wood, Chuck
    Woodfield, George
    Wood, Milton
    Woods, Buck
    Woods, Harry
    Y
    Young, Artie
    Young, Otis
    Younger, Tank
    Actresses
    A
    Alix, Mae
    Allen, Anna Lou
    Allen, Clarice
    Anderson, Allegretti
    Anderson, Charles Mrs.
    Anderson, Ester
    Anderson, Inez
    Anderson Myrtle
    Andre, Carol
    Appley, Hilda
    Arnold, Jeanne
    Attaway, Ruth
    Ayler, Ethel
    Bailey, Pearl
    Bartless, Barbara
    Beard, Renee (Child)
    Bearden, Bessye
    Beavers, Louise
    Belafonte, Julie
    Bellamy, Madge
    Benson, Rochelle
    Berger, Santa
    Bilbrew, A.C. Mrs.
    Billiups, Billie
    Blakeley, Rubie
    Blandino, Althea
    Blondell, Juanita
    Bowles, Lottie
    Bowman, Laura
    Boyd, Mildred
    Boyd, Mona
    Boyer, Anise
    Boyer, Elizabeth
    Brewer, Sherri
    Brooks, Eunice
    Brooks, Hazel
    Brown, Anne
    Brown, Chelsea
    Brown, Ester
    Brown, Honey
    Brown, Marie
    Browning, Haroldine J.
    Bruce, Gladys
    Bruce, Millie
    Bufford, Daisy
    Burgess, Dorothy
    Burke, Georgia
    Burns, Fannetta
    Burns, Sandy
    Burwell, Evelyn
    Burwell, Myra
    Bush, Anita
    Butler, Sarah
    Calomee, Gloria
    Canty, Marietta
    Capers, Virginia
    Carr, Georgia
    Carroll, Diahann
    Cartens, Mariane
    Cash, Rosalind
    Chavence, Janice
    Chrisman, Gertrude
    Clarke, Alberta
    Claude, Suzan
    Cleaver, Zeldo
    Clements, Lynda
    Clough, Inez
    Cohee, Regina
    Cole, Carol
    Cole, Celeste
    Cole, Mildred
    Coleman, Paralee
    Collins, Valerie
    Comfort, Madi
    Conley, Betty Jean
    Conn, Irene
    Cooke, Louise
    Cooley, Isabelle
    Cornell, Ann
    Cote, Bobbie
    Cox, Jewell
    Craig, Fay
    Cross, Ruth
    Crozier, Helen
    Cunningham, Edna
    Curry, Mary
    Dandridge, Dorothy
    Dandridge, Ruby
    Dandridge, Vivian
    Dave, Peggy
    Davenport, Mildred
    David, Kim
    Davis, Arette (Child)
    Davis, Elvira (Baby Sanchez
    Davis, Jean
    Dawn, Marpessa
    Deane, Althea
    Dee, Ruby
    DeKnight, Fannie Bell
    DeLavallade, Angelle
    Dempsey, Pauline
    Deslonde, Jackie
    Desmond, Cleo
    DeSousa, Ruth
    Dillard, Mimi
    Dodson, Gloria
    Doscher, Doris
    Drake, Carolle
    Driver, Frances
    Dumont, Dorothye
    Dumont, Yvonne
    Dunbar, Dorothy
    Dunbar, Louise
    Ellis, Evelyn
    Ellis, Patricia
    Elzy, Ruby
    Evans, Estelle
    Everett, Francine
    Falana, Lola
    Feder, Marjorie (Child)
    Fiegert, Elfie
    Fisher, Gail
    Fitzgerald, Ella
    Forsyne, Ida
    Foster, Daisy
    Foster, Frances
    Foster, Gloria
    Foster, Lesa
    Francis, Vera
    Franklin, Louise
    Frederick, Maxine
    Fullwood, Yemiko (Child)
    Gallo, Loray
    Garcia, Lea
    Gee, Lottie
    Gorgas, Alice
    Gray, Jane
    Grayson, Jessica
    Green, Cora
    Greene, Laura
    Guyse, Sheila
    Hall, Beulah
    Hall, Iris
    Hall, Juanita
    Hamilton, Josie
    Hamilton, Kim
    Hamilton, Lynn
    Harbin, Suzette
    Harris, Beverly
    Harris, Dorothy
    Harris, Edna Mae
    Harris, Jeni
    Harris, Lucretia (Rogers)
    Harris, Lola
    Harris, Theresa
    Hartman, Ena
    Hathaway, Maggie
    Hayes, Rosalind
    Haynes, Hilda
    Haynes, Sylvia
    Heath, Velma
    Hecht, Jenny
    Hemsley, Estelle
    Henderson, Frances
    Henderson, Lee
    Henderson, Maye
    Hendy, Gloria
    Hendy, Jeannine
    Henriquez, Sylvana
    Holly, Ellen
    Horn, Lena
    Hoskins, Jane F. (Child)
    Howard, Ester
    Howard, Gertrude
    Hughes, Helen Oates
    Hundley, LaJuene
    Hyson, Roberta
    Jackson, Mary Ann
    James, Olga
    Jenkins, Margaret
    Jessye, Eva Mae
    Johnson, Myra
    Jones, Beulah Hall
    Jones, Edna Mae
    Hones, Hazel
    Jones, Margurite
    Jordan, Rhoda
    Kalana, Thias Nehli
    Kellerman, Annette
    Kelly, Mabel
    Kelly, Paula
    Kennedy, Florence
    King, Jean
    King, Mabel
    Kitt, Eartha
    Lamont, Carol
    LaNoire, Rosetta
    Laster, Georgia
    Laster, Gwendolyn (Child)
    LaVasse, Vera
    Lavassor, Vera
    LaVerne, Jane (Child)
    Lawrence, Mittie
    Legon, Jeni
    Lehr, Anna
    Lein, Sandra
    LeNoire, Rosetta
    Lewis, Sybil
    Leyba, Claire
    Limyou, Jeanna
    Lincoln, Abby
    Lincoln, Rosa Lee
    Linticum, Alice
    Louise, Anna
    Luna, Donyale (Peggy Freeman)
    Lynn, Mauri
    McCrea, Maxie
    McCrey, Maxine F.
    McCurdy, Anna Marie
    McDaniel, Etta
    McDaniels, Hattie
    McDuffie, Lizzie
    McQuire, Alberta T.
    Machen, Yvonne
    Mackey, Lola
    McKinney, Nina Mae
    MacLachlan, Janet
    McNair, Barbara
    McNeil, Claudia
    McQueen, Butterfly (Thelma)
    McQuire, Lurene
    Mantee, Dolores
    Marquand, Tina
    Matthew, Inez
    Matthews, Bessie
    Mays, Betti
    Meser, Enid
    Meyers, Pauline
    Michelle, Janee
    Mickey, Arlene
    Mills, Allison
    Mills, Gertrude
    Mithcell, Abbie
    Moore, Ada
    Moore, Gertrude
    Moore, Joanna
    Moore, Juanita
    Moreland, Marcella
    Morrison, Dorothy
    Morrison, Lori(Child
    Morrison, Pearl
    Morton, Edna
    Moseley, Lillian
    Moses, Lucia
    Myers, Pauline
    Neal, Consuela
    Nealy, Frances
    Nicholas, Alice
    Nichols, Michelle
    Noisette, Kathleen
    Nordman, Marilyn
    Norman, Maidie
    Norsette, Katherine
    O'Brien, Florence
    Offley, Hilda
    Oliver, Edna Mae
    Pace, Jean
    Pace, Judy
    Parker, Delores
    Patton, Jonella
    Patton, Marguerite
    Paul, Betsy
    Penn, Jane
    Peters, Edith
    Peters, Hattie
    Peters, Virginia
    Peterson, Lenka
    Peterson, Monica
    Pickens, Albertine
    Pilot, Beatrice
    Pink, Janice
    Piper, Delores
    Pittman, Elina
    Poree, Anita
    Powell, Bertha
    Preer, Evelyn
    Premice, Josephine
    Prendergast, Tessa
    Price, Naomi
    Rae, Etta
    Randolph, Amanda
    Randolph, Barbara
    Randolph, Lillian
    Rawls, Jamey (Child)
    Reese, Della
    Rentie, Freida
    Rhue, Madlyn
    Ribeiro, Hilda
    Rice, Versia
    Richards, Beah
    Richards, Mary
    Robinson, Doris
    Rosamond, Patricia
    Rowland, Nita
    Russell, Alice B.
    Sawyer, Ruth
    Shawn, Shirley
    Shuford, Abbie
    Simms, Hilda
    Smith, Alma
    Smith, Bernice
    Smith, Connie
    Smith, Ethel
    Smith, Grace
    Smith, Mildred Joanne
    Smith, Muriel
    Smith, Vivian
    Snelson, Gertrude
    Snowden, Carol
    Snyder, Gladys
    Sparks, Fay
    Spencer, Edith
    Spivey, Victoria
    Stanton, Mary or Mayra
    Steele, Geraldine
    Storell, Viola
    Stubbs, Louise
    Sultewan, Naomi
    Sutton, Susie
    Swan, J.A.
    Sykes, Brenda
    Taylor, Beatrice
    Taylor, Beverly
    Taylor, Francine
    Thompson, Anita
    Thompson, Blanche
    Thompson, Viola
    Todd, Beverly
    Torrence, Lena
    Tucker, Loretta
    Tuggle, Ora
    Tulley, Ethel
    Turner, Mae
    Tyson, Cycely
    Uggams, Leslie
    Van Engle, Dorothy
    Ventura, Vivian
    Villere, Dawn
    Wade, Ernestine
    Wallace, Royce
    Wan, Sul Te Madam
    Warren, Odessa
    Washington, Flora
    Washington, Florence
    Washington, Fredi
    Washington, Hannah
    Washington, Hazel
    Washington, Mildred
    Waters, Ethel
    Waters, Mira
    Welch, Elizabeth
    West, Geraldine
    White, Loray
    Wilcox, Ipenetta
    Wilkes, Mattie
    Williams, Anna Zette
    Williams, Augusta
    Williams, Irene
    Williams, Ivory
    Williams, Onida
    Wilson, Irene
    Winston, Catherine
    Winters, Pamela
    Yancy, Emily
    Young, Harriette (Dee Dee)
    Young, Jackie
    Dancers
    Aquabello, Francesco
    Aiken, Vanoye
    Ailey, Alvin
    Alston, Barbara
    Aul, Carmen
    Avalos, Ricardo
    Baker, Josephine
    Bates, Peg Leg
    Berry Brothers
    Bowen, Clarence
    Bower, Jamie
    Bryant, Marie
    Buck & Bubbles
    Butterbeans & Suzie
    Carter, Carol
    Coles & Atkins
    Collette, Florine
    Collins, Janet
    Cooper, Blondell
    Cooper, Cecelia
    Costosa, Marie
    Covan, Willie
    Cutler, Byron
    Dancer, Earl
    Daniels, Leroy
    Davis, Sammy Sr.
    DeLavallade, Carmen
    DeLavallade, Yvonne
    Dudley, Mary
    Duncan, Arthur
    Dunham, Katherine
    Edwards, Jodie (Butterbeans)
    Edwards, Suzan
    Ellington, Mercede
    Ellis, Lucille
    Folana, Lola
    Fear, Clifford
    Fontaine, Joan
    The Four Step Brothers
    Goldoni, Lelia
    Gomez, Tommy
    Hardaway, Rose
    Harper, Delores
    Hawker, John
    Holder, Geoffrey
    Horton, Lester
    Jackson, Arlene
    Johnson & Dean
    Johnson, Carleton
    Johnson, Charles
    Johnson, Louis
    La Redd, Cora
    Lindsay, Roy
    Marchant, Claude
    Maxey & Sumler
    Mendez, Julio
    Menon, Gypsy Dawn
    Montgomery, Jean
    Morris, Lenwood
    Neal, Frank
    Nicholas Brothers
    Nicholas, Harold
    Powers, Ollie
    Richardson, Walter
    Robinson, Clarence
    Robinson, Juli
    Rollins, Lois
    Sanders, Charles
    Savage, Archie
    Savoy Ballroom
    Scrivner, Calla
    Seabrook, Joan
    Sebree, Charles
    Sibley & Epps
    Sides, Pat
    Smith, Gus
    Snowden, Carolyn
    Standifer, Glenn
    Strozier, Othella
    Trenier Twins
    Tucker, Snakehips
    Ultria, Lenore
    Wade, Boots
    Walden, Barbara
    Wallace, George
    Washington, Fred Buck
    Wells, Dicky
    Westbrook, Nancy
    Williams, Lavina
    Williams, Urul
    Musicians/Singers
    Adams, Faye
    Adderly, Julian Cannonball
    Adderly, Nat
    Afro-American Concert Band
    Anderson, Cat William
    Anderson, Marion
    Armstrong, Lil
    Arnau, Brenda
    Bailey, Thurmond
    Baker, LaVern
    Ballard, Florence
    Barefield, Eddie
    Basie, Count
    Bassey, Shirley
    Bechet, Sidney
    Belafonte, Margurite
    Ben Hur, Jorge
    Benton, Brook
    Berry, Chuck
    Biggs, Howard
    Black Pattie
    Blair, Sally
    Blake, Eubie
    Bland, Billy
    Bland, James
    The Blossoms
    Booker T & the M.G.'s
    Bostic, Earl
    Bradley, Harold
    Bradford, Perry
    Bradley, Jimmy
    Broonzy, Big Bill
    Brown, James
    Brown, Ray
    Brown, Ruth
    Browning, Razaf
    Bryant, Joyce
    Buck 'n Bubbles
    Bricktop (Ada Smith)
    Burleigh, Harry T.
    Calhoun, Arthur
    Calloway, Blanche
    Calloway, Chris
    Campbell, Choker
    Carlisle, Una Mae
    Carney, Harry
    Carol, Connie
    Carpenter, Thelma
    Carroll, Nansi
    Carson, Tee
    Carter, Benny
    Carter, Mel
    Cato, Minto
    Cavanaugh, Page Trio
    Cele, Willard
    Chaino
    The Charioteers
    Charles, Ray
    Checker, Chubby
    Cleveland, James
    The Clovers
    Cobb, Arnett
    Cochran, Wayne
    Cole, Cozy
    Cole, Ike
    Cole, Maria
    Cole, Natalie
    Cole, Robert
    Coleman, Ornette
    Collette, Buddy
    Collins, Claude
    Cook, J. Lawrence
    Cook, Will Marion
    Cooke, Sam
    Cooper, Clarence
    Cox, Ida
    Creach, John - Papa John
    Curtis, King
    Cuttler, Byron
    Daniels, Jerry
    Davis, Miles
    Day Ilene
    The Dell Vikings
    The Delta Rhythm Boys
    DePriest, Jimmy
    Dett, Nathaniel
    The Diamonds
    Dickerson, Carroll
    Dixie Jubilee Femine Quartet
    Dixon, Charles
    Dixon, Dean
    Dobbs, Mattwilda
    Dobbs, Baby
    Dodds, Johnny
    Dodson, Marge
    Dolphy, Eric
    Domino, Fats
    Doqui, Bob
    Dumas, Barbara
    Dyson, Rita
    Dyson, Ronnie
    Eckstine, Billy
    Eckstine, June
    Edwards Sisters
    Edwards, Jodie
    Eldridge, Roy
    Ellington, Duke
    Ellington, Edna
    Ellington, Mercer
    Elliott, Lu
    Emporers of Song Quartet
    Erby, Morris
    Evans, Russell (Bob)
    The Fifth Dimensions
    Fltecher, Tom
    Florence Mills Association
    The Four Tones
    Franklin, Aretha
    Friends of Distinction
    Fuqua, Charlie
    Gailliard, Slim
    Garner, Erroll
    Gaye, Marvin
    Gibbs, Georgia
    Gillespie, Dizzy
    Gillespie, William
    Golden Gate Quartet
    Gonzales, Paul
    Grant, Cy
    Grant, Earl
    Gray, Dobie
    Gree, Ed
    Green, Joe
    Griffin, Bessie
    Hall, Adelaide
    Hall Johnson Choir
    Hamilton, Chico
    Hamilton, Jimmy
    Hampton, Lionel
    Hancock, Herbie
    Handy, W.C.
    Harper, Toni
    Harpo, Slim
    The Harptones
    Harris, Ace
    Harris, Dimples
    Harris, Wynomie
    Hawes, Hampton
    Hawkins, Coleman
    Hayes, Roland
    Haywood, Donald
    Henderson, Fletcher
    Henderson, Rick
    Henderson, Rosa
    Heyward, Ann
    Hibbler, Al
    Higgenbotham, J.C.
    Hiller Sisters
    Hines, Earl Fatha
    Hines, Ernest
    Hite, Les
    Hodges, Johnny
    Holliday, Billie
    Hopkins, Linda
    Horne, Lena
    House, Son
    Hubbard, Freddie
    Hudgens, Johnny
    Hughes, Revella
    The Impressions
    The Ink Spots
    Jackson, Hal
    Jackson, Mahalia
    Jackson, Quentin
    Jacquet, Illinois
    Jemison, Diane
    Johnson, Bubber
    Johnson, J.J.
    Johnson, J. Rosamond
    Johnson, Mae
    Johnson, Marv
    Jones, Booker T.
    Jones, Carl
    Jones, Elvin
    Jones, HappyOroville
    Jones, Herb
    Jones, Quincy
    Jones, Richard M.
    Jones, Tamiko
    Jordan, Louis
    Joyce, Brenda
    Joyner, Matilda
    Kenny Bill
    King, B.B.
    Knight, Marie
    Lancelot, Sir
    Lane, Ruby
    LaRue, Reese
    Lee, Dinah
    Lee, Marci
    Leighton, Mauri
    Lester, Ketty
    Lewis, John
    Lewis, Meade Lux
    Lincoln, Abbie
    Lipscomb, Mance
    Lutcher, Nellie
    Lymon, Frankie
    Lynn, Gloria
    McBroom, Marcia
    McCray, Margeret
    McFerran, Robert
    McLean, Jackie
    McNiles, Calypso
    McRae, Carmen
    McVeys Orchestra
    Makeba, Miriam
    The Mariners
    Masakela, Hugh
    Mathis, Johnny
    Matthews, Charles
    Mayfield, Percy
    Maynor, Dorothy
    Mbulla, Letta
    Meadows, Joyce
    Mercer, Mae
    Ma Rainey
    Middleton, Velma
    Milburn, Amos
    Miller, Johnny
    Miller, Norma
    Mills Brothers
    Mills, Everett
    Mills, Florence
    Mitchell, Abbie
    Mitchell, Ben
    Mitchell, Louis
    Modern Jazz Quartet
    Monk, Thelonius
    Moore, Oscar
    Moore, Paula
    Moore, Phil
    Moore, Wild Bill
    Moorefield, Olive
    Moro, Tony
    Morton, Jelly Roll
    Mosby's Dixieland Blue Blowers
    Moten, Benny
    Moten, Etta
    Murphy, Rose
    Nance, Ray
    Nash, Johnny
    Nash, Lavenia
    Nelson, Oliver
    Newborn, Phineas
    Noel, Hattie
    Oliver, King
    The Orioles
    Page, Hot Lips
    Parham, Tiny
    Parker, Dorothy
    Payne, Benny
    Pennima, Richard (Little Richard)
    Peters Sisters
    Pettiford, Oscar
    Powell, Bud
    Price, Leontyne
    Price, Lloyd
    Procope, Russell
    Prude, Terrell
    Quinn, Carol
    The Raelettes
    Rahn, Muriel
    Rainey, Massachusetts
    Razaf, Andy
    Redd, Freddie
    Redding, Otis
    Reed, Freddie
    Roach, Max
    Roberts, Rocky
    The Robins
    Robinson, Sugar Chile Frankie Isaac